

Producer / Project Manager









Highly adaptive and multi-disciplined Producer / Project Manager with a technical and design background. Experienced in leading interdisciplinary teams in fast-paced environments. Keen eye for quality and risk assessment. Passionate about elevating teams to excellence by ensuring smooth processes and pipelines.

Industry Experience

Junior Producer | Lionfish Studios Pte Ltd – *Multiple Projects*Mar 2021 – Present

- Managing communications between development team and stakeholders
- Managing in-house and outsourced development teams across 5 projects
- Overseeing project milestones and releases
- Coordinating project development with <u>multiple cross-functional</u> teams
- Leading company-wide transition to a Sprint-based development cycle

Production Intern | gumi Asia Pte Ltd - *Final Fantasy Brave Exvius* Sept 2020 – Feb 2021

- Responsible for Design team's <u>Sprint Planning</u> and follow ups with <u>Jira</u>
- Maintained event lists for content updates with <u>Google Sheets</u> and <u>Confluence</u>
- Assisted Associate Producer in integrating <u>new ticketing workflow</u>
- Began department-wide initiative to streamline and automate workflows
 - Reduced Jira ticket creation / modification time by 50%

On-Campus Experience

Teaching Assistant | DigiPen Singapore – *Game Production Class* Sept 2019 – Mar 2020

Advised ~10 student teams on project management and game production

Academic Projects

Producer, Editor Programmer, Cinematics Designer

Kindred | Sept 2019 – June 2020, 35 Weeks | 11 Person Team

- 3D narrative game developed on a custom C++ engine and editor with C# scripting
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Communicated game's direction across team members and lecturers
- Adopted <u>Agile</u> methodology with weekly <u>Scrum</u> meetings and <u>Kanban</u> boards
- Created <u>cross-department workflows</u> for better communication
- Finalist in multiple categories, DigiPen Game Awards 2020

Producer, Engine & Editor Programmer

Mega Macho Brothers | Sept 2018 – Apr 2019, 30 Weeks | 7 Person Team

- 2D co-op action platformer developed on a custom C++ engine and editor
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Worked with lecturers and team members to resolve conflicts
- Awarded Unity Best Sophomore Game, DigiPen Game Awards 2019

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Game Design

DigiPen Institute of Technology, Singapore Sept 2017 – Apr 2021

- Dean's Honour List, Fall '19
- Exchange Student DigiPen Redmond, Summer '19

Skills

Soft Skills

Effective Communication Team Management
Problem Solving Detail Oriented
Conflict Resolution Project Ownership

Management Methods

Agile Scrum Kanban

Management Software

Jira Trello
Confluence HacknPlan
Slack Discord
Google Suite Microsoft Suite

Software & Tools

Git / SVN Microsoft Office
Visual Studio Visual Studio Code
Unity Unreal Engine
Custom Game Engine(s) Zapier

Programming Languages

C / C++ C#
Python JavaScript
Rust Lua

Spoken Languages

English Mandarin

For more details on my projects, see my Portfolio!